[(844) 503-4CBD](tel:8445034223) Tues-Fri : 10-6pm / Sat-Sun: 10-4pm

0

You have 0 items in your cart

Go To Shopping

* Quick Links
    * Tinctures
    * Specialty Tinctures
    * Topicals
    * Gummies
* Learning Center

[(844) 503-4CBD](tel:8445034223) Tues-Fri : 10-6pm / Sat-Sun: 10-4pm

* Quick Links
    * * * ### _Pure, Lab tested CBD is the BEST feeling ever!_
                
        * * Tinctures
        * * Specialty Tinctures
            * Topicals
            * Gummies
            * #### Cart
                
            * 
    
    * * * RESEARCH | SCIENCE | STANDARDS | QUALITY
                ----------------------------------------
                
* Learning Center

[](https://nanoplanetcbd.com/cart/)0

You have 0 items in your cart

Go To Shopping

Privacy Policy
--------------

Last updated February 01, 2023

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to nanoplanetcbd.com, and NanoPlanet CBD and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to NanoPlanet CBD include nanoplanetcbd.com. The NanoPlanet CBD website is a eCommerce site. By using the NanoPlanet CBD website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

#### Collection of your Personal Information

In order to better provide you with products and services offered, NanoPlanet CBD may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:  

* First and Last Name
* Mailing Address
* E-mail Address
* Phone Number

If you purchase NanoPlanet CBD products and services, we collect billing and credit card information to pass through our encrypted, secure credit card merchant processor (First Data) via Authorize.net. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. **No credit card data is ever stored on the NanoPlanet CBD servers.**

NanoPlanet CBD may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your:

* Age
* Gender
* Location

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through NanoPlanet CBD's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products, subscriptions or services. These may include: (a) registering for an account; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

#### Use of your Personal Information

* NanoPlanet CBD collects and uses your personal information to operate and deliver the services you have requested.
* NanoPlanet CBD may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from NanoPlanet CBD and its affiliates.

#### Sharing Information with Third Parties

* NanoPlanet CBD does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
* NanoPlanet CBD may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to NanoPlanet CBD, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
* NanoPlanet CBD may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on NanoPlanet CBD or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of NanoPlanet CBD; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of NanoPlanet CBD, or the public.

#### Tracking User Behavior

NanoPlanet CBD may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within NanoPlanet CBD, in order to determine what NanoPlanet CBD services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within NanoPlanet CBD to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

#### Automatically Collected Information

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by NanoPlanet CBD. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the NanoPlanet CBD website.

#### Use of Cookies

The NanoPlanet CBD website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize NanoPlanet CBD pages, or register with NanoPlanet CBD site or services, a cookie helps NanoPlanet CBD to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same NanoPlanet CBD website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the NanoPlanet CBD features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the NanoPlanet CBD services or websites you visit.

#### Security of your Personal Information

NanoPlanet CBD secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. NanoPlanet CBD uses the following methods for this purpose:

* SSL Protocol
* SSL Certificate by Comodo
* Website Security by iThemes Security
* Additional Security by WP Security

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

#### Right to Deletion

Subject to certain exceptions set out below, on receipt of a verifiable request from you, we will:

* Delete your personal information from our records
* Direct any service providers to delete your personal information from their records

**\*Please note**: We may not be able to comply with requests to delete your personal information if it is necessary to:

* Complete the transaction for which the personal information was collected, fulfill the terms of a written warranty or product recall conducted in accordance with federal law, provide a good or service requested by you, or reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform a contract between you and us
* Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity; or prosecute those responsible for that activity
* Debug to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality
* Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise his or her right of free speech, or exercise another right provided for by law
* Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act
* Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when our deletion of the information is likely to render impossible or seriously impair the achievement of such research, provided we have obtained your informed consent
* Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with your expectations based on your relationship with us
* Comply with an existing legal obligation or otherwise use your personal information, internally, in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which you provided the information.

#### Children Under Eighteen

NanoPlanet CBD does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of eighteen. If you are under the age of eighteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

#### Disconnecting your NanoPlanet CBD Account from Third Party Websites

You will be able to connect your NanoPlanet CBD account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR NANOPLANET CBD ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED IN THIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THIS FEATURE.

You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. No user third-party account credentials are ever saved by NanoPlanet CBD. If a user chooses to share information, data, and/or links to NanoPlanet CBD products via social networking sites, no data is retained here.

#### E-mail Communications

From time to time, NanoPlanet CBD may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication.

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from NanoPlanet CBD, you may opt out of such communications by "replying **STOP**" or "clicking on the **UNSUBSCRIBE** button.".

#### Changes to this Statement

NanoPlanet CBD reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our website, and/or by updating any privacy information. Your continued use of the website and/or Services available after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.

#### Contact Information

NanoPlanet CBD welcomes your questions and/or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that NanoPlanet CBD has not adhered to this Statement, please contact the NanoPlanet CBD website admin at:

**NanoPlanet CBD**  
1475 SE 14th Ave  
Portland, Oregon 97214  
E: support@nanoplanetcbd.com  
T: (844) 503-4CBD

Effective as of September 01, 2021

Go Back

CBD4CANCER Program
------------------

Join our CBD4CANCER program and our products are instantly discounted to $25 per product, any product sitewide, no limitations. If you have a current diagnosis... you qualify! Find out more here: [CBD4CANCER Program](https://nanoplanetcbd.com/cbd4cancer/)

**Secure Payments**

### Site Links

**Site Programs**  
\- [Affiliate Program](https://nanoplanetcbd.com/cbd-affiliate-program/ "CBD Affiliate Program")  
\- [Wholesale Program](https://nanoplanetcbd.com/wholesalecbd/ "Wholesale CBD")  
\- [CBD4CANCER Program](https://nanoplanetcbd.com/cbd4cancer/ "CBD4Cancer Program")

### Contact Info

Coos Bay, OR 97420  

**Store Hours**  
– Order online 24/7/365  
– Orders received ship same day whenever possible

Copyright ©2020-2023 386 LLC. All Rights Reserved.

##### Cookies Policy Opt-Out

**NanoPlanet CBD** does not sell your personal data. We use cookies to improve user experience and analyze website traffic.  
By clicking "Accept" or continuing to use this site, you agree to our website's cookie use as described in our [Cookie Policy](https://nanoplanetcbd.com/cookie-policy). You may change your cookie preferences any time by clicking the "**Manage Consent**" button located in the bottom right corner of this site.

Accept Reject All [View Full Policy Here](https://nanoplanetcbd.com/cookie-policy/)×

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Functional

 Functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

Performance

 Performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

Analytics

 Analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

Advertisement

 Advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

Others

 Others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

SAVE & ACCEPT

Powered by [](https://www.cookieyes.com/)
